Shut up! There's no way! She so did not do that.
Oh, yes, she did.
Yes!
Hurry up! We're gonna get in trouble if we're late again.
No, I'm trying.
So, you went ahead and bought them?
Yep, brand new shoes. I'm gonna be super fast today.
Just you wait. You'll be eating my dust.
Oh, whatever.
Miss Takeyama, please return to the faculty room as soon as possible.
Yeah, that one made me cry a lot, too.
Why is he in the library?
You girls are late again.
We're sorry.
Get changed immediately and start running laps.
Okay.
And get a better attitude.
So, Senna, where are you going now?
I did bring that movie I was talking about if you wanted to see it.
What's wrong, Senna?
I forgot my gym clothes.
Do you want to go back to that same store again?
I was just about to ask you the same question.
Oh, my God, we almost died.
He is totally the worst.
Okay, then let's do it last.
You
Kyo, you're so exaggerating.
I'm totally not.
I'm telling you, they both almost died, like, right there in the hallway.
Um, no, it's not.
Like, at all.
Who's in there talking?
She must be on a cell phone or something.
Come on, you always say that.
I know that girl.
How many times do I have to tell you?
It never happened.
No, it didn't.
She's in my class.
Yozara something.
Mikazuki, I think.
But I've never heard her laugh like that in class.
Or, well, ever.
She always looks pissed as hell.
Kind of like she's about to murder someone.
I've never really seen her talk to anybody.
Crazy.
Hold on, this is officially weird.
She's not talking on the phone at all.
I told you, I'm not giving up on that.
What the hell?
Well, who's she talking to?
Is there somebody hiding in there?
So why not?
A girl talking to an invisible thing in an empty classroom at dusk.
But you can't just sit there and wait for it.
You know, this sounds exactly like the beginning of a book I just started reading.
Next, after various obstacles, I discover her secret and ultimately defend her by fighting and killing a thing not of this world.
Then we would naturally, uh, fall in love.
I guess.
All right.
You know what, Tomo?
I think I do remember that.
Huh?
That's what she usually looks like.
But she was so cute when she was laughing.
What do you want?
I, I was just wondering, do you like see ghosts and stuff?
What?
Uh, no, cause ghosts don't exist.
Well then, who have you been talking to?
You were watching me?
Look, I was having a conversation with my best friend ever.
She's made of air, okay?
You have an air friend?
What the crap is that?
It's exactly what I said it was.
You've heard of an air guitar before, haven't you?
She's like that, but cooler.
So let's see, you pretend someone is there and talk to them like they're talking back to you?
I'm not pretending.
Tomo exists, you big jerk.
See, she's right here next to me.
For example, Tomo and I were just talking about this one time when we went to a theme park back when we were in middle school.
This group of guys was totally hitting on us while we were there.
I mean, it was ridiculous, so I decided to pretend one of them was going to be our hot new home room teacher.
You just said you were pretending.
Shut up.
The point is, it really happened.
Oh, really?
How much of it really happened?
The part where I was in middle school?
So only 99% of it was a complete lie?
I was hoping the amusement park would at least turn out to be real.
Seriously?
Who would want to go to an amusement park by themselves?
You just admitted you were alone.
Stop.
Go ahead and get over it, because Tomo is unbelievably adorable.
That chick is off a rocker.
This cannot end well.
So this is really about self-preservation.
What does that look for?
I don't know.
Wouldn't it be a lot easier for you to just, you know, make a real friend instead?
Not an air friend like adorable Tomo, but an actual living person.
Yeah, well, I would if I could, thank you.
Shocking that you can't.
And just who are you to talk?
You're that new kid everyone's afraid of, isn't that right?
I've been at this school for well over a month now.
I'm hardly a new kid.
What's your name?
It's Kodoka Hasegawa.
It seems to me you have no right to say anything about having friends, Kodoka.
First name basis already?
So an entire month has passed and you still haven't made a single friend yet?
Wouldn't you say that's a little pathetic?
Hey, you only have an air friend.
Where the hell do you get off?
There's no reason to be rude to her.
My friend Tomo is adorable and crazy smart.
And she's also an amazing athlete and the absolute best friend a girl like me could ever hope to have.
What's more, she would never even dream about stabbing me in the back.
It's not a mystery.
There's nothing else I can do.
I don't know how to make friends.
Yeah, I'm not really that great at it either.
Did you not have any friends at your old school?
Of course I did.
Don't you still talk to them?
He said he would text me, but I haven't heard from him.
Maybe you misunderstood and just, like, thought you were friends.
Maybe shut up.
Fine, then.
You know, if you wanted, you could try to pay someone to be friends with you.
No, that's so lame.
Come on.
A small stipend every week for spending time together at school.
Like a prostitute?
What is that, a friendstitute?
No, it's a basic contract.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with a contract.
Or you could just ask someone to be your friend.
I've seen people do that on after-school specials, but I don't really get it.
You ask someone to be friends, and the moment they agree, a friendship is suddenly formed.
Even if you'd never spoken to each other before then.
What if you never even talk after getting approval?
Can you still consider that person to be your friend?
Congrats!
Awesome!
Yeah, well, I guess I can't really blame you.
It's not my thing, either.
Besides, I'm pretty independent, so it's not like I need to have any friends.
Right.
Not having friends must be so hard on that poor girl.
Condescension has to be my least favorite thing in the whole world.
Well, I can understand.
For whatever reason, people think if you don't have a lot of friends, there's something wrong with you.
I don't think that's true, though.
At least I hope it's not.
I'm perfectly fine being alone.
Having a few general acquaintances at school, those types of superficial friends are enough for me.
Yeah, but still, I have to admit, it would be nice to have a real friend.
What about school clubs?
No way.
Why is that a bad idea?
Because we're in our second year.
Club-based friendships have already been established.
It'd be too embarrassing to join one now, not to mention completely obvious.
I guess that's true.
If you're only joining a club to make friends and not because you share an interest,
you're only going to screw with their dynamic.
You'll end up being the one loser member with nothing to offer.
Why would they even want you to join?
She's got a point.
I'd only join a club to meet people.
I don't really have any other reason.
And I would hate to bug them if they were already friends.
That would suck.
That's perfect.
A club!
Huh?
See you later, Kodaka.
Hmm.
Why my hair looks like this?
Oh, well, my late mother was English, so I get it from her.
I mean, hey, it's not really PC, but have at it.
Thank you.
It was pretty difficult, but I guess time heals all wounds, right?
My father decided to go abroad for work.
I started going to St. Chronica's Academy in Toyashi then.
But my first day of school, I took the wrong bus and ended up getting there really late.
When I finally arrived at the academy, I was on the verge of tears.
Compared to crusading armies, Saladin's army...
Hello.
I'm, uh, the transfer student.
Okay, great.
My name is Kodaka.
Nice to be here.
Oh, no.
Ms. Osada.
Did he just attack her?
Delinquent much?
She's new here.
Want some of his hair?
Oh, I forgot my book.
Here, take mine.
Oh, thanks.
By the evening of my first day, the whole school had heard the rumor.
I was a thug who stole the book of the poor girl sitting next to me.
It's been a month since then,
and I still haven't been able to redeem myself for that first day fail.
See you later, Kodaka.
What a weird girl.
I did like that she said my first name.
I haven't heard that at school yet.
Nice.
In equations of the nth degree,
there will always be a root.
As a result, the root of n...
The usual.
What's wrong with her now?
Kodaka, follow me, please.
Holy crap, she talked to it.
To that Hasekawa creep?
Oh, well, give me a second.
Okay, what's going on?
I've gone through all the formalities and crap.
What are you talking about?
I created a new club.
Since we can't join a club that already exists,
well, it seemed only logical for me to go make a new one.
Yeah, I get it.
In a new club, you don't have to stress out about making things awkward for anybody.
So what kind of club did you end up making?
The Neighbors Club.
The Neighbors Club?
That's right.
In compliance with God's instructions, we embrace everyone as neighbors,
deepen friendships on a spiritual level, yada, yada, yada,
work together and treat everyone with the kindness that God would want or whatnot.
Will a club like that actually get approved, though?
Are you kidding me?
This school is full of suckers.
Throw in God or working hard?
They cannot get enough of that stuff.
Religion is always an easy sell.
All right, so then what's this Neighbors Club actually going to do?
It's going to help us make some damn friends.
And we can avoid getting a bunch of pity fates from the other students while we're at it.
We'll load up on as many shallow acquaintances as we can
and then keep our eye out for people we could tolerate as real friends.
Interesting plan of attack, I guess.
Well, good luck.
Why are you wishing me good luck?
You're a member, too.
Huh?
You left before I could get the paperwork to you yesterday.
So I just went ahead and filled out your registration.
Say thank you.
You did what?
You're very welcome.
Now let the club activities begin.
You know you want to.
Wait, where are we going?
This is the chapel's common room.
You sure this is okay for the club to use?
The club advisor okayed it.
That makes it okay.
Okay, and do they plan on advising us on how to make some new friends, too?
Probably not.
Huh?
The club advisor in question is Sister Maria.
She doesn't have a lot of friends herself.
Then why did she become our advisor?
I get intimidated by people who look like they have a lot of friends.
So I decided to go with her.
You are something else.
I know.
We need to get more members.
What is this?
It's our poster.
We're going to put them up on bulletin boards all over the school.
We are?
But it doesn't describe anything about what the club does.
Shows how much you know.
Try looking at it diagonally, genius.
Diagonally?
Oh, I see.
Friends wanted?
Get it now?
What did you put a lame joke in there for?
It's not a joke.
Come on, think about it.
Anyone who is always on the lookout for friends is bound to see that message hidden in the poster.
Huh?
But that's not all.
I tried to draw a scene from that famous song.
You know the one about making 100 friends and eating rice balls at the top of Mount Fuji?
Even if they don't catch the diagonal sentence, the drawing should totally clue them in on what we're about.
And you're sure it's not a joke?
Positive.
Let's hang these bad boys up.
On to the next one.
Hey.
Hey, are you positive you really want to be friends with someone who's desperate enough to understand this poster?
So your desperation is fine, but theirs isn't?
Uh, doublestandard.com.
You know that's not what I meant.
And you know that I have an actual name.
But you keep calling me you all the damn time.
It's really starting to piss me off.
Oh, I'm sorry.
So is Mikazuki all right?
Yozura.
You can use my first name.
Fine.
I'll call you that.
Yo-yozura.
Uh.
Come on.
Don't you have a nickname or something easier for me to say?
I do.
Did?
Look, I'm not going to tell you what it was, Kodaka.
Why not?
Because only real friends use nicknames with each other.
I know.
I'm late.
I'm sorry.
Man, I'm exhausted.
So, I think we should start regular activities tomorrow.
Yeah, I seriously doubt anyone's going to want to join our club after looking at that poster.
Oh, really?
Because that sounds like a new member to me.
What?
We just got back from putting them up.
This is the neighbor's club, right?
I'd like to join, please.
Wrong number.
Hey, what?
Yozura.
You're right.
We should start now.
That's not it.
She wants to join, and she's a girl who could be your best friend, which is kind of what you're
looking for, isn't it?
Don't be ridiculous.
Oh, my God.
That blonde in your hair is totally showing right now.
You've already met my best friend, and her name is Tomo, remember?
Okay.
Why did you slam the door in my face?
I said I want to join your group.
Die, princess!
No!
So, you guys know each other already?
No, we do not.
Her name is Sina Kashawazaki, and she is the daughter of the academy president.
She's in class 2-3, and all the boys worship her.
We do not need to be friends with princess wannabes.
Oh.
Yeah, I've heard about her.
Of course.
Why is it you give a girl blonde hair and huge knockers and guys fawn all over them?
It's disgusting.
What?
I'm not fawning all over anybody.
Ooh, she's glamorous and can play sports really well and make straight A's.
Sina has been at the top of the class since last year in every freaking subject.
She can't be that perfect.
There has to be something wrong with her!
This chick needs serious therapy.
She is not giving up.
Why are you being so mean to me?
The only thing I'm trying to do is join your stupid-ass club!
If you're here to spy on us, go away!
I'm not spying on you!
I saw your poster that said you were looking for some friends!
I want to join because I want friends too, okay?
Yeah, everybody knows how perfect I am.
I'm super smart, really good at sports, and obviously I'm totes gorgeous.
Only if cow udders are gorgeous.
Life must be hard for you having that flat chest.
Oh, please.
It's not like I'm that flat.
Well, you know what they say about a pair of tangerines.
You might as well have nothing.
If I murdered all the women who had larger breasts than me, then I would have a relatively
large rack in comparison, now wouldn't I?
I don't suppose you would like to become the glorious first sacrifice of my lofty plan?
Please stop.
You came here because you wanted friends, right?
That's right.
What are you talking about?
You've got guys around you all the time.
Those are just servants.
I want more than that.
It'd be nice to have girlfriends for once in my life.
That way, when teams are formed in class or when we leave school for a field trip, I'll
have friends I can hang out with.
Oh, come on.
You're surrounded by boys all the time.
Why don't you hang out with them?
I don't want to hear anyone say that to me ever again.
I just want to have some real friends.
Now that you mention it, I have heard girls can be pretty mean to other girls, especially
if they're pretty and popular and intelligent.
Considering you're a thug, you're a lot smarter than I thought you'd be.
I don't mind stepping on you if you want me to.
What the hell's wrong with you?
Why would I want you to do that?
I don't know.
The boys in my class usually love it.
Don't tell me you're looking for something more than that.
What a pervy creep.
I am not a stupid thug or a pervy creep.
What the crap are you looking at?
Mew, this situation is perfect for you guys.
With both of you here, you can make friends with each other, yeah?
What?
Whatever.
Why would I ever, like ever, want to be friends with somebody like her?
And why would I ever, like ever, want to be friends with someone like her?
What do you mean by that?
They just met?
How can they hate each other so much already?
Your eyes are slanted too, you idiot.
I know, but my eyes are slanted too.
So, you want to stop and get food?
You know I do.
The usual.
Please go dive.
No, you please go dive.
Actually, just get out of here.
What now?
No, I'm joining this club.
You'll just have to deal with it.
No, you're not.
Get out.
No, you get out.
So there.
This is the first day of the Neighbors Club.
One person joined, bringing us to a grand total of three members.
I guess most people would consider that a smooth start.
Most people would be wrong.
Hey, I rented this awesome movie yesterday.
Oh my God, it was hilarious.
Which one was it?
I can't remember the name.
You know the one where the girl thinks these people are her friends, but they're like totally the opposite?
And these two continued.
You know, you are a terrible person.
Well, that's better than being an idiot.
Hello, I'm at the top of our class.
Oh, someone give her a trophy.
Lady Meat actually knows how to study.
You bitch! I can have my daddy expel you.
Aren't you a little embarrassed to still be using the word daddy at your age?
You need to quit this club.
I can't quit my own club.
Since when was it just your club?
Next, there's no God in the electric world.
Look, they agreed on something.
See you next time.
ushm